https://noabuse.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Chrysalis understands how important it is to maintain your privacy. Please read below to find out more about Chrysalis’ terms and conditions of the use of its website www.noabuse.org. If you have any questions regarding Chrysalis’ privacy policy, please call us at 602-955-9059.
Chrysalis defines personal information as anything that identifies you as an individual, e.g., your name, email address, phone number or address.
Chrysalis provides you with the option to submit your email address to sign up for our electronic newsletters or when you make an online contribution. Any correspondence sent to this email address will provide you with the opportunity to opt out.
Your IP address may provide Chrysalis with broad demographic information about your viewing history on Chrysalis’ site; Chrysalis does not retrieve personal information.
When personal information is shared with Chrysalis, it will not be rented, shared, traded or sold to other individuals or companies.
By using noabuse.org, you are consenting to Chrysalis’ privacy policies.
2055 W. Northern Ave., Phoenix, AZ 85021
Our NewsletterEmail *Select list(s) to subscribe to Example: Yes, I would like to receive emails from Chrysalis. (You can unsubscribe anytime)Constant Contact Use.By submitting this form, you are consenting to receive marketing emails from: Chrysalis, 2055 W. Northern Ave., Phoenix, AZ, 85021, http://www.noabuse.org. You can revoke your consent to receive emails at any time by using the SafeUnsubscribe® link, found at the bottom of every email. Emails are serviced by Constant Contact
Affiliations
We are licensed through the Arizona Department of Health Services.
Chrysalis is nonprofit organization dedicated to individuals and families impacted by domestic abuse. Through a comprehensive trauma-informed approach of services, Chrysalis aims to prevent domestic abuse.
Careers
Media
Events
Legal
Privacy Policy
© Copyright 2018 Chrysalis -
noabuse.org
FACEBOOK
